we are bringing the whole end-to-end
solution right from the hardware to the
mobile apps right that a vehicle owner
can use to view his data view his
vehicle but most importantly as a
platform we plan to build things like
Predictive Analytics and others which
will allow a car owner not to just think
of his vehicle with a black box but look
at it like a travel companion and be
able to manage all aspects of his life
cycle that's what we're getting okay we
have a lot of computer a lot of
Microsoft platform and we've been around
for almost a decade now so
it's a platform that has seen
International customer as well as
Indians right right
um
be a lot of collaboration going on and
everybody who taught me pretty much the
same place so even if you look at
elements I think the language spoken
needs to be quite Universal from
audience tell us about how this platform
is taking it to the next level
[Music]
at different Power frames how does this
and that's where we look at ourselves
making a dent now only if we look at any
kind of elementic solution they're about
tracking a vehicle and find out where
you went and that's about it so we kind
of moved on from that phase right today
we have 4G 5G is coming in soon we're
able to collect a lot of data from a
vehicle and make some Intelligent
Decisions on the cloud side so you
almost have unlimited cloud
processing capability which is not
available in the past
cool
where we are excited about the full new
data consumption feature that is
particular platform uh tell me now data
is I think perhaps the most crucial
thing you know everybody can generate
gigabytes and gigabytes of data but if
you can't comprehend it I think uh
you're absolutely right most of the data
that you see is usually going right you
have to be able to pull those signals
out of that data right and an automotive
world makes it complex vehicle goes at
2000 RPM for 70 percent of its time
right and that's just going to stay the
same now here we need to look at that
particular data and pull out those
specific segments out which will make
sense right right and that data
selection that we call it internally in
automotive interpreter is able to
interpret Automotive data which makes
sense and that's when we're able to kind
of differentiate this in a big way
that's the whole signal to boys ratio
how has the availability of or the new
rule out now or the fifth generation of
uh internet service providers
allowed you to penetrate into the market
a little bit more deeper in terms of
customers that now it is actually a
little more relevant so
I personally think that price is just
coming along it all changes right due to
a large accent right right now you have
become data consumers and no longer the
service consumers right I mean one of
the largest telephones in India causes
of a data company right right and that's
how things are changing right with paiji
there is this whole excitement about
more things that can be done which were
a challenge in the past so something
like sending a firmware update to a
vehicle even if your health bands most
health bands crash today when they're
downloading a big tank of data and their
experiences can't do the vehicle that is
okay if it happens so Health bad but
can't wait until Vehicles right and
those attritions those fears to
submitter prices will take out of the
equation they are leading to a better
adoption from the oems to allow this for
the income right right uh what are the
key metrics that your platform allows
your end customers to govern and is it a
standard option today or actually
continues to be largely an optional
equipment from the original perspective
or from the end user
it is becoming more and more relevant
and that's where we see everybody
adopting this in a much more having a
Passion
deployment that was various what you
want to say from the previous side so
when you open commercial vehicles then
again then small commercials
foreign
[Music]
that's where we are really really
focused on because India and Indian
consumers are becoming aware of privacy
their rights yes
right so you when there is a there is
sufficient fear and sufficient
understanding of privacy that these
worldwide chatting apps need to make
advertisements to explain their security
right right and that's where this data
action is going to do a lot of play we
are also looking at all the legislation
that have been planned from the India's
platform we already gdpr compliant and
others but other laws that are going to
come into India we are already making
them up when the OEM doesn't have to
think of compliance we take care of the
compliance
detection
vulnerability
yes absolutely so that's also something
that almost everybody is becoming aware
of luckily before us we started working
with the insurance sector in 2016.
they've been extremely paranoid about
data data we have very stringent audit
processes we will probably be the first
telematics company to have a dedicated
Chief security officer okay so that is
why would you have achieve Secretary of
2016 but we had one because
right so we take that very seriously and
one of the latest offering is one where
over the air and stuff which is
encrypted has independent certificate
management
everything that you can think of from an
Enterprise grade stable and scalable and
secure platform that we have that is
also for older vehicles yes yes
absolutely so we have two types of go to
markets one is an oem fitment and one is
an aftermarket after marketing for your
fitment is one way really right and do
you cater to or assist Elite operators
in the initial stages of using those
platforms and trying to
give them a proper use case that over a
six month period or a year long period
this is what will help you achieve yeah
yeah so we are very much Roi driven
right some of the some of the most
important use cases we get is like can
you help me become more safer can you
help me reduce fuel theft can you help
me reduce misuse of vehicles and even we
before before we go live we ask them
what are your current numbers and then
over a period of six months or a year we
show them how we've been able to help
them achieve that Roi and solve that
difference to them and you're right if
we leave and
taking screenshots and sharing which is
so different so then we we have a
success team now in-house that every
time a customer comes an account manager
and success managers assigned to them
and they've hand told them for the first
six months so they cannot become much
more proficient in the users
conversation now uh what is the overall
penetration of telematics like there is
foreign
[Music]
thank you